The innocent 13-year-old girl from South Africa
has been brought to The SCOAN unable to walk due to a musculo-skeletal condition.
The medical report from The New Life Medical Centre attests to the fact that
little Miracle's movements are severely limited and that she is in constant pain.
As a result of the acute musculo-skeletal condition, she has to be co-managed
by a specialist of neurological unit in Botswana.
Due to her to her inability to walk by herself Miracle was brought to the church stretching out in a car.
Let's find out exactly what happened to this little girl who should be running about at play or in school,
and has led to this terrible condition of hardly being able to move at all.
My name is Khubai Miracle. I am 13 years old.
I come from South Africa.
I cannot walk due to musculo-skeletal condition.
It started when I was at school.
A teacher beat me on my leg; I couldn't walk, from there I collapsed.
I have been urinating on myself and messing myself for the past one month.
My mum has been by my side helping me.
I have not been doing anything.
I cannot stand, bend or sit down nicely.
I cannot go to the toilet by myself.
I always urinate on myself.
When my mum is not there, I cannot get to the toilet, I will mess myself on the bed.
But when my mum is here, she will always help me to go to the toilet.
I feel heart-broken and sad because this has affected my life.
I cannot go to school.
It is hard for me to carry my own things.
I cannot focus on schooling due to this problem that I have.
I sometimes cry, praying to God to help me walk.
I have gone to all hospitals both in Botswana and South Africa.
I have gone to all sorts of churches - no solution.
I came to know about The SCOAN by watching it on Emmanuel TV.
I saw people in wheelchairs getting healed.
I believe that Jesus will heal me and I will be an example to all other kids.
My name is Augusta Nkechinyere. I am from Mbaise, Imo state.
I stayed in South Africa.
She is my daughter, my only child.
She has a musculo-skeletal problem.
She is unable to walk since the teacher flogged her at school.
She fainted and started passing through this problem.
She has not been walking, she cannot open her legs, fold them or sit.
She cannot go to the toilet.
If I am not there she urinates on herself.
It has even affected my job.
I have taken her to so many hospitals in South Africa and Botswana and even to some churches.
There was no solution.
I always watch Emmanuel TV; I even sleep with it on.
I saw how the man of God is healing people in wheelchairs and cases worse than hers.
I believe that this is the place where my daughter will be healed.
I believe that the God of T.B. Joshua will heal my daughter.
My daughter will not go back to South Africa like this with the same condition.
We pray with you that the Lord Jesus will use his able servant, seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua
to set your daughter free from this problem of inability to walk
due to musculoskeletal condition in Jesus' name.
Amen.
HEALING TIME
I cannot walk due to getting beaten at school.
I got paralysed in my back and I can not walk due to musculoskeletal condition.
Man of God, please help me, I cannot walk!
How old are you?
I am 13 years old.
I am from South Africa. Man of God, please, help me; I cannot walk due to musculoskeletal condition.
That is my only child; she urinates on herself.
The teacher flogged her at school; she came back and collapsed.
She messes herself, she can not do anything.
I am the one who is bathing her, feeding her, doing everything.
Prophet T.B. Joshua Ministering Prayer and Healing In Jesus' Name
Healing In Jesus' Name
Stand up.
I can walk! Thank you, Jesus, I can walk!
Healed In Jesus' Name
This is the power of prayer in the name of Jesus Christ.
The evidence of God's miracle in this little girl's life is her rising and walking.
Thank you, Jesus!
TESTIMONY TIME
And right now we can see our sister is here in our midst walking to the glory of God.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ.
My name is Khubai Miracle.
I am 13 years old and I come from South Africa. I am South African citizen residing in Botswana.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN is that I could not walk due to musculoskeletal condition.
This has affected my life in a way that I could not do things by myself.
I would always urinate on myself.
No one was there to help me. The only person that was there to help me is my mum.
And every time I would look at other kids there, they will be walking, playing around and
this really hurts because I couldn't manage to do what the other kids were doing out there.
So we saw what happened when Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you.
Can you just describe to us - at that moment, what happened in your body, as he prayed for you?
As he prayed for me, I felt my body - the chain was breaking into pieces.
I could not feel any chain that was locking my legs again.
People of God, let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
So you mean when you came in, it was like your legs were locked together, as if they were in chains.
But the moment Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for you, you felt as if the chains were broken
and you began to walk.
Yes.
Glory be to God! And ever since then, just tell us - it has been one week now.
What are the changes you have seen in your body, in your life?
I can now do all the things by myself. I can bath myself.
I can bend down, I can sit down, I can walk.
Amen! Let's put our hands for Jesus Christ!
We can see the joy of the Lord on our sister's face.
We can see what she can now do that she couldn't do before due to this musculoskeletal condition.
We can see her moving freely. This someone that actually came in a vehicle because
she was unable to walk by herself but today we see to the glory of God that she is freed.
And sister, what is your word of advice to viewers around the world?
Before I say my advice, I would like to thank daddy, seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua
for healing me. May God give him more strength.
I would like to thank the workers out there. May God give them strength to do more work.
Miss Kubhai Miracle Healed Of Inability To Walk
My advice is that you should always have faith in God.
Believe in God because you should always know that God is always by your side.
No matter your problems, no matter anything that is wronging you in your life.
Believe in God. He will change your life.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
My name is Augusta Nkechinyere. I am a Nigerian residing in Botswana.
The beautiful girl that's standing beside me is my beloved daughter, my only child.
I am so happy for what God used seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua to do in her life.
I am so happy. I don't know how to express my feelings.
All my friends both in Botswana, South Africa - they were calling, they were happy, even my parents.
I'm so happy.
My advice to the whole world is that you should have faith in God. Believe in God.
Believe that there is nothing that God can not do. Now my daughter can do everything.
She can bath herself, she can feed herself, she can walk around, sit, sing, dance. She is so happy.
She is very very happy. All the things that she has not been able to do before ,
now she is doing everything.
Wow, so before you were the one assisting her to do everything, even to go to the toilet.
Yes, I was the one assisting her with my sister.
She is the one always helping me to assist her. Anywhere she is now, she is watching.
Let God fulfill all her heart desires for her, in Jesus' name.
Amen! Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time.
So we give glory to God for the wonderful transformation in the life of our little sister here
and we pray that God will give you all the grace to continue to stay close to Jesus,
make His Word the standard for your life and we know that this family is coming back with
even more wonderful testimonies in Jesus' name.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ one more time!
After Miracle was healed by God Almighty from the musculoskeletal disorder that had rendered
her unable to walk, she and her mother were supported by Prophet T.B. Joshua
and Emmanuel TV Partners with the sum of $2,000.
My name is Khubai Miracle
I am 13 years old. I am a South African citizen residing in Botswana.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN is that I could not walk due to musculoskeletal condition.
My daddy seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua prayed for me - now I can walk and I'm very happy.
My name is Augusta Nkechinyere. I'm Nigerian. I'm from Mbaise.
I'm very very happy, God used seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua to heal her.
I am so happy. My heart is full of joy. Full of happiness.
Amen. Thank you very much. And right now as we all know what The SCOAN stands for.
The man of God in his usual kind gesture in line with Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world
has actually been touched by the healing of your daughter and said he wouldn't just
allow her to go that way without giving her the necessary support for her upkeep.
That is why the man of God has decided with Emmanuel TV Partners all over the world to give
you and your daughter the sum of $2000.
Overflowing with joy and gratitude to God for the transformation in their lives,
Miracle and her mother gladly receive the gift of $2000 and the Mirror book to nurture them
materially and spiritually.
Thank you, Emmanuel TV. Thank you, seniour Prophet T.B. Joshua. Thank you for what you have done for us.
You have given me a new life. God will reward you, God will bless you,
protect you, guide you, give you more strength to do this job.
I came with a problem with my daughter, God used you to deliver her, to heal her.
I didn't pay anything, I didn't spend anything the way I have been going to all the hospitals, to other churches -
they charged me. I spent money, now I didn't pay anything.
And look at what he gave me. He gave me the sum of $2000 to support my daughter.
He even paid for our accommodation, feeding us since we came.
Now we are going back, he supported us with the sum of $2000.
Amen. Thank you very much. And the man of God did not only want to stop at this point in time.
And he said he wants to give your daughter scholarship from the very stage she is right now
in her educational level to university level.
I'm speechless, I don't know how to thank him. I don't know how to thank man of God.
I don't know how to thank him. May the good Lord bless him for me. He has done a lot for me.
He saved my life. He saved me by giving my daughter a scholarship and the sum of $2000.
Which is a big relief for me which I did not even expect.
I have not even dreamt about it. He has done something that nobody can ever do for me.
I'm so happy. Thank you, daddy, thank you. May God bless you. Thank you, daddy. I love you.
I would also like to sing a song.
Never give up
No, never
Never
No, no never
Never give up
In times of troubles, in times of sorrows
No, never
Never give up
Miss Khubai & Mother With 2000$
We love you man of God. We love you. Thank you, daddy.
TT: Monica Asefa
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov